<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Space Management on SpiderOak Share File Sharing Documentation</title>
    <link>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Space Management on SpiderOak Share File Sharing Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>© 2019 &lt;a href=&#34;https://spideroak.com&#34;&gt;SpiderOak Inc.&lt;/a&gt; All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 15:12:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewing Space Members</title>
      <link>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/1viewmembers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 15:15:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/1viewmembers.html</guid>
      <description>Users of a Space may be audited by the admins of that Space. (Note that a Space becomes a Shared Space once another team member is added to it. If no team members are added to a new Space, then the Space remains a Personal Space for the user who created the Space.)
How do I view Space members?  First, select the correct Space via the &amp;ldquo;Shared Spaces&amp;rdquo;. (&amp;ldquo;Test Space&amp;rdquo; is selected in the screen shot below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Members to and Removing Members from a Space</title>
      <link>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/2addingmembers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 15:19:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/2addingmembers.html</guid>
      <description>Managing Space membership by adding and removing Team Members from Spaces ensures that only the desired team members have access to shared data. A Space admin may add a Team Member to a Shared Space, or a personal space, but when the Team Member is added to a personal space, it becomes a Shared Space. (A Space where the creator is the only member remains a Personal Space, but when another team member is added to the space it becomes a &amp;ldquo;Shared Space&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promote a Member to a Space Admin</title>
      <link>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/3spaceadmin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 15:23:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shareapp.tk/admin/space/3spaceadmin.html</guid>
      <description>Space admins have the ability to add, remove, and promote fellow members to admins within the given Space. A Space admin cannot add, remove, or promote members on the team level.
How do I promote a member to a Space Admin?  Navigate to the correct Shared Space. (You must be in the space to administer it, and users must be members to be promoted.)
 In the Shared Space, select the dropdown arrow next to the Space name above, and then select &amp;ldquo;Space Members.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>